<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Toon Timbermont</title>
    <link>https://toontimbermont.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Toon Timbermont</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Datt BV</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:45:29 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://toontimbermont.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://toontimbermont.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 17:46:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toontimbermont.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About This Blog This blog collects my thinking and public learning on topics that I am really passionate about: personal development, technology and start-ups.
About Me From Datt.be, I provide consulting services in these 3 areas. Some projects I worked on:
Tax-on-Web Vitalink Skryv Some companies I worked for:
Accenture HealthConnect, Smals Skryv, VandenBroele ING, BNP Paribas Fortis, &amp;hellip; Flemish Government, Belgian Government See LinkedIn for more info about me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Tips on How to Start a Startup</title>
      <link>https://toontimbermont.github.io/posts/5-tips-start-startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:45:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toontimbermont.github.io/posts/5-tips-start-startup/</guid>
      <description>Starting a startup is a bet. A big bet. You&amp;rsquo;ll spend a lot of time and effort on it, possibly your money as well&amp;hellip; Which is daunting! So you&amp;rsquo;ll want to prepare for your journey.
Before starting Skryv, I read plenty of blog posts &amp;amp; books, talked to quite a few people and followed a support track. Out of that, I distilled my startup checklist, starting with the why, creating the legal entity and finding the initial idea and team to get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://toontimbermont.github.io/privacy_cookie_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toontimbermont.github.io/privacy_cookie_policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy &amp;amp; Cookie Policy This privacy &amp;amp; cookie policy applies to DATT BV, further referred to as DATT.
DATT respects and protects your privacy. In this privacy &amp;amp; cookie policy we will explain which personal data DATT collects, how and why we use it and how we protect your data.
Processing personal data by DATT DATT is responsible for the processing of personal data. This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for toontimbermont.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
