<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Toon Timbermont</title>
    <link>https://toontimbermont.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Toon Timbermont</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Datt BV</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 17:45:29 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://toontimbermont.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3 books that shape my organisational thinking</title>
      <link>https://toontimbermont.github.io/posts/3-books-organising-software-development-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 17:45:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toontimbermont.github.io/posts/3-books-organising-software-development-teams/</guid>
      <description>As a software architect, project lead, and tech startup co-founder, I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered many challenges that are disguised as technical choices or issues.
And while tech is often a factor, the organizational issues beneath these challenges are just as critical or even more critical to address.
Here are three inspiring books that have shaped my thinking on how to navigate interpersonal and organizational challenges in a tech environment.
5 Dysfunctions of a team Working with people is not always easy and goes wrong in many ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why and How I use Obsidian as a 2nd Brain</title>
      <link>https://toontimbermont.github.io/posts/why-how-i-use-obsidian/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 12:20:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toontimbermont.github.io/posts/why-how-i-use-obsidian/</guid>
      <description>Your mind is for having ideas, not holding them. — [David Allen](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/David_Allen_(author)
Why a Digital 2nd Brain? I do not remember everything. I forget. Sometimes this is a good thing, but often not. You do want to forget a bad memory, but not that important task!
I have ideas. A lot of them. At various and random places and moments. Trying to remember these ideas and associations creates cognitive load I do not want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://toontimbermont.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 17:46:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toontimbermont.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About This Blog In this blog, I write articles triggered by questions or conversations I have with inspiring people. Each blog post is typically a more extended answer to something I discussed with them and consider worthwhile to share publicly. Please note that these posts are 100% my own opinions and points of views.
About Me As a kid, I loved building things.
As a teenager &amp;amp; student, I loved organising things, both at local &amp;amp; international level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Tips on How to Start a Startup</title>
      <link>https://toontimbermont.github.io/posts/5-tips-start-startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:45:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toontimbermont.github.io/posts/5-tips-start-startup/</guid>
      <description>Starting a startup is a bet. A big bet. You&amp;rsquo;ll spend a lot of time and effort on it, possibly your money as well&amp;hellip; Which is daunting! So you&amp;rsquo;ll want to prepare for your journey.
Before starting Skryv, I read plenty of blog posts &amp;amp; books, talked to quite a few people and followed a support track. Out of that, I distilled my startup checklist, starting with the why, creating the legal entity and finding the initial idea and team to get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://toontimbermont.github.io/privacy_cookie_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://toontimbermont.github.io/privacy_cookie_policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy &amp;amp; Cookie Policy This privacy &amp;amp; cookie policy applies to DATT BV, further referred to as DATT.
DATT respects and protects your privacy. In this privacy &amp;amp; cookie policy we will explain which personal data DATT collects, how and why we use it and how we protect your data.
Processing personal data by DATT DATT is responsible for the processing of personal data. This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for toontimbermont.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
